**Call now for FREE devices, $0 activation fees, and FREE shipping! [(888) 298-4894](tel:(888)%20298-4894)**

[Call Today (888) 298-4894](tel:(888)%20298-4894)

**Privacy Policy**
==================

My Connected Caregiver built the My Connected Caregiver app as a Free app. This SERVICE is provided by My Connected Caregiver at no cost and is intended for use as is.

This page is used to inform visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service.

**At Connected Caregiver, we respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it.**
---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) explains the types information we collect about those who visit our Website, how we use it, the conditions of disclosure, and how we keep it secure. By using our Website, you are agreeing to be bound by this Policy.

_When we use the term “Website,” we are collectively referring to myconnectedcaregiver.com, the Connected Caregiver mobile applications (including our applications that you download through the Apple or Google app stores), remote physiological monitoring and safety monitoring devices that we provide to you if you are a customer, and/or the portal.myconnectedcaregiver.com; all are considered our Website for purposes of this Policy and this Policy applies to all personal data collected or received from you through any of the foregoing methods._

Any questions regarding this Policy and our privacy practices should be sent by email to [\[email protected\]](https://myconnectedcaregiver.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or by writing to Connected Caregiver at 10 Cadillac Dr., Suite 350, Brentwood, TN 37027. Alternatively, you may call 877-774-4363

**Consent to Connected Caregiver’s use of your personal data**
--------------------------------------------------------------

By accessing our Website or providing us with your personal data, you are consenting to its collection and use in accordance with this Policy. If you do not agree with our privacy practices, you are under no obligation to use our Website or our remote physiological monitoring devices or safety monitoring devices.

This Policy applies to information we collect:

* On myconnectedcaregiver.com and portal.myconnectedcaregiver.com;
* Through our mobile and desktop applications you download (whether from us or via the Apple or Google app stores), which provide dedicated non-browser-based interaction between you and us;
* In email, text, and other electronic messages between you and the Website;
* When you use one of our remote physiological monitoring or safety monitoring devices; and/or
* When you interact with our advertising and applications on third-party websites and services, if those applications or advertising include links to this Policy.

This Policy does not apply to information collected by any third party, including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from the Website.

**Protecting the privacy rights of children**
---------------------------------------------

Our Website is not intended for children 16 years of age and younger. No one age 16 or younger may provide any personal information to or on the Website or through any of the other means described above. We never knowingly collect personal information from children under 16. If you are under 16, do not use or provide any information on this Website or through any of its features, register on the Website, make any purchases through the Website, use any of the interactive or public comment features of this Website, or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, phone number, email address, or any screen name or user name you may use. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 16 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 16, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://myconnectedcaregiver.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

California residents under 16 years of age may have additional rights regarding the collection and sale of their personal information. Please see [Your California privacy rights](https://myconnectedcaregiver.com/privacy/#CA) for more information.

**Information we collect**
--------------------------

We collect information from and about users of our Website and remote monitoring and safety monitoring devices, including information:

* By which remote monitoring or safety monitoring device users may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, email address, phone number, date of birth, gender, language, caregiver and insurance information and, in the case of safety monitoring devices, location and direction of travel (“**personal information**”);
* That is about you but does not individually identify you; and/or
* About your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website and other services, and usage details.

**How we collect information**

1. Directly from you when you provide it to us. This includes:
    * Information provided at the time of registering to use our Website, subscribing to our service, posting material, or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our Website or our services. Records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses), if you contact us;
    * Your responses to surveys that we might ask you to complete for quality assurance purposes;
    * Your search queries on the Website;
    * Information collected by our remote monitoring and safety monitoring devices; and
    * Information you choose to publish or display (hereinafter, “**post**”) on public areas of the Website, or transmit to other users of the Website, or to third parties (collectively, “**User Contributions**”).

1. Automatically as you navigate through our Website (including when you use our mobile and desktop applications and our remote physiological monitoring and safety monitoring devices). This includes:

1. * Usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies, web beacons and other tracking technologies. See [Information we collect through automatic data collection technologies](https://www.verustat.com/privacy/#a563456745) for detailed information.
    * Physiological information (like blood pressure, weight, etc.).
    * Your location and activity levels.

1. From third parties, for example, our business partners or others listed on your Connected Caregiver account.

**Information we collect through automatic data collection technologies**
-------------------------------------------------------------------------

As you navigate through and interact with our Website, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including:

* Details of your visits to our Website, including traffic data, location data, logs, and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website; and
* Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, and browser type.

The information we collect automatically may include personal information, or we may maintain it or associate it with personal information we collect in other ways or receive from third parties. It helps us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to:

* Estimate our audience size and usage patterns;
* Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Website according to your individual interests;
* Speed up your searches; and
* Recognize you when you return to our Website.

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

* **Cookies (or browser cookies).** A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website.
* **Flash Cookies.** Certain features of our Website may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from, and on our Website. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies. For information about managing your privacy and security settings for Flash cookies, see Your choices about how we use and disclose your information.
* **Web Beacons.** Pages of the Website and our emails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit the Company, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an email and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity).

**How we use your information**
-------------------------------

The information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information is used:

* In accordance with HIPAA Privacy and Security Rules (with respect to personal health information)
* To fulfill the purposes for which you provide it, including to provide you with information, products, or services that you request from us
* To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us
* To best present our Website and its contents to you
* To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide though it
* To enable you to participate in interactive features on our Website if you chose to do so
* To administer and expand our business activities, including making available other products and services to you and our other customers
* To notify you about important changes to our Website, products or services or special offers that we think you will find valuable
* Call (833) 210-9591 or (833) 210-9596 with any questions

**What we may share**
---------------------

We may disclose aggregated information about our users and information that does not identify any individual.

Personal information that we collect, or that you provide, may be disclosed in the following ways:

* In accordance with the HIPAA Privacy and Security Rules (with respect to personal health information)
* To fulfill the purposes for which you provide it
* To contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business
* To enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes
* To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request
* To assist or support a third party’s theft investigation involving any of our remote monitoring or safety monitoring devices or a third party’s theft prevention efforts relating to such devices;
* To prevent, investigate, detect or prosecute criminal offenses or attacks on the technical integrity of the Website;
* To fulfill a product or service order;
* To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by us about our users is among the assets transferred
* With your written authorization.

We may use third parties to facilitate our business, including, but not limited to, sending email and processing credit card payments. In connection with these offerings and business operations, such third parties may have access to your personal information for use in connection with such business activities. 

As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer, email, and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or any dissolution.

We may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the law or comply with legal process served on us or authorized dealers; (b) protect and defend our rights and property, the Website, the users of the Website; or (c) act under circumstances to protect the safety of users of the Website, us, or third parties.

We may use your personal information, such as information about your location, demographic information, medications taken, and medical conditions, to show you advertisements that we believe will be more relevant to you. Note, when we do this, we do so without telling advertisers who you are. We instead allow promotional partners to tell us things like their business goal and the kind of audience to develop a profile for people likely to be interested in or benefit from their products and services. We then show their advertisements to our users who match that profile.

We also provide promotional partners with reports about the performance of their advertisements to help them understand how people are interacting with their advertising content. For example, we may provide general demographic and interest information to promotional partners to help them better understand their audience. We don’t share information that directly identifies you (information such as your name or email address or specific location that by itself can be used to contact you or identifies who you are) unless you give us specific permission. 

**Anonymized, de-identified and aggregate information**
-------------------------------------------------------

We may anonymize your personal information or de-identify personal health information in a way that meets the HIPAA de-identification standard, in each case so that the applicable data will no longer be identifiable to you. We may also combine such anonymized and de-identified information with that of other users to create aggregate anonymized and de-identified data. Any data rendered anonymous or de-identified in accordance with the foregoing ceases to be subject to the terms of this policy and becomes our property, to be used in any lawful manner at our discretion (which may include sharing such anonymized and de-identified information with our partners and/or affiliate organizations), provided in no event will we disclose or use such information in a manner that would identify you personally, as an individual.

**Your choices about how we use and disclose your information**

We also provide you with choices regarding the personal information you share with us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:

* **Tracking Technologies.** You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. To learn how you can manage your Flash cookie settings, visit the Flash player settings page on Adobe’s website. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.
* **Your Content and Sharing Records.** If you are a registered user, the Website allows you to share your own records with others. For example, you may choose to invite your family members or friends access to your records on the Service so that they can track your progress. You understand that by giving them permission to access your records, that they will have the ability to use, reproduce, distribute, display, transmit, or publish your content. You understand that sharing your records in this manner is voluntary, done at your direction, and that you may revoke your permission given for any individual at any time.

California residents may have additional personal information rights and choices. Please see [Your California privacy rights](https://myconnectedcaregiver.com/privacy/#CA) for more information.

Nevada residents who wish to exercise their sale opt-out rights under Nevada Revised Statutes Chapter 603A may submit a request to this designated address: [\[email protected\]](https://myconnectedcaregiver.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). However, please know we do not sell data triggering this statute’s opt-out requirements.

**Accessing and correcting your information**
---------------------------------------------

You can review and change your personal information by logging into the Website and visiting your account profile page.

You may also email us at [\[email protected\]](https://myconnectedcaregiver.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) to request access to, correct or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. Know that we cannot delete your personal information except by also deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.

California residents may have additional personal information rights and choices. Please see [Your California privacy rights](https://myconnectedcaregiver.com/privacy/#CA) for more information.

**SMS/US short code terms**
---------------------------

1. When users opt into Connected Caregiver SMS communications, they can expect to receive what they have agreed to receive, including reminder notifications and alerts when readings fall outside of doctor-prescribed ranges, etc.
2. You can cancel the SMS service at any time. Just text “STOP” to the short code. After you send the SMS message “STOP” to us, we will send you an SMS message to confirm that you have been unsubscribed. After this, you will no longer receive SMS messages from us. If you want to join again, just sign up as you did the first time and we will start sending SMS messages to you again.
3. If you are experiencing issues with the messaging program you can reply with the keyword HELP for more assistance, or you can get help directly at 877-774-4363.
4. Carriers are not liable for delayed or undelivered messages.
5. As always, message and data rates may apply for any messages sent to you from us and to us from you. Mesage Frequency will vary. If you have any questions about your text plan or data plan, it is best to contact your wireless provider.
6. Connected Caregiver does not share personal identifiable information collected through SMS/short code to either affiliated or non-affiliated third parties for its own marketing purposes.

**Your California privacy rights**
----------------------------------

If you are a California resident, State law may provide you with additional rights regarding the use of your personal information, including a right to knowledge, access, and deletion of their personal information under the California Consumer Privacy Act. California consumers also have a right to opt out of the sale of their personal information by a business and a right not to be discriminated against for exercising one of their California privacy rights. [Learn more about your California privacy rights](https://oag.ca.gov/privacy/ccpa) 

_NOTE: we do not sell personal information to businesses or discriminate against any individual for exercising his or her privacy rights._

**California’s “Shine the Light” law (Civil Code Section § 1798.83)**
---------------------------------------------------------------------

This permits users of our app who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please email [\[email protected\]](https://myconnectedcaregiver.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection), or mail a letter to Connected Caregiver, 10 Cadillac Dr., Suite 350, Brentwood, TN 37027.

_Note: we do not disclose your personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes._

**Do Not Track (DNT)**
----------------------

Connected Caregiver does not track its customers over time and across third party websites to provide targeted advertising and therefore does not respond to Do Not Track (DNT) signals. Third parties cannot collect any other personally identifiable information from Connected Caregiver’s websites unless you provide it to them directly.

**Data Security**
-----------------

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal information.

We restrict access to personal information to our employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve the Website. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

However, we cannot guarantee the security of any personal information, or information collected from the Website. Despite our efforts to secure such information, it may be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by a breach of our physical, technical, and procedural safeguards. You use our Website at your own risk. If we learn that your personal information has been disclosed to an unauthorized person, we will use reasonable efforts to attempt to notify you.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. We urge you to be careful about providing information in public areas of the Website, like message boards. The information you share in public areas may be viewed by any user of the Website.

While we continue to work hard to protect personal information, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100 percent secure and we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to us over the Internet. Transmitting personal information over the Internet is done at your own risk. This Policy addresses only our policy and procedures. We are not responsible for the privacy policies of third parties, including but not limited to those whose web sites may be linked to the Website.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**
---------------------------------

If we make any changes to how we treat our registered users’ personal information, we will notify you by email to the primary email address specified in your account and/or through a notice on the Website home page. The date this Policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable email address for you, and for periodically visiting our Website and this Policy to check for any changes.

**Your California privacy rights**
----------------------------------

If you are a California resident, State law may provide you with additional rights regarding the use of your personal information, including a right to knowledge, access, and deletion of their personal information under the California Consumer Privacy Act. California consumers also have a right to opt out of the sale of their personal information by a business and a right not to be discriminated against for exercising one of their California privacy rights. [Learn more about your California privacy rights](https://oag.ca.gov/privacy/ccpa) 

_NOTE: we do not sell personal information to businesses or discriminate against any individual for exercising his or her privacy rights._

**California’s “Shine the Light” law (Civil Code Section § 1798.83)**
---------------------------------------------------------------------

This permits users of our app who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please email [\[email protected\]](https://myconnectedcaregiver.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection), or mail a letter to Connected Caregiver, 10 Cadillac Dr., Suite 350, Brentwood, TN 37027.

_Note: we do not disclose your personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes._

**Do Not Track (DNT)**
----------------------

Connected Caregiver does not track its customers over time and across third party websites to provide targeted advertising and therefore does not respond to Do Not Track (DNT) signals. Third parties cannot collect any other personally identifiable information from Connected Caregiver’s websites unless you provide it to them directly.

**Data Security**
-----------------

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal information.

We restrict access to personal information to our employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve the Website. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

However, we cannot guarantee the security of any personal information, or information collected from the Website. Despite our efforts to secure such information, it may be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by a breach of our physical, technical, and procedural safeguards. You use our Website at your own risk. If we learn that your personal information has been disclosed to an unauthorized person, we will use reasonable efforts to attempt to notify you.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. We urge you to be careful about providing information in public areas of the Website, like message boards. The information you share in public areas may be viewed by any user of the Website.

While we continue to work hard to protect personal information, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100 percent secure and we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to us over the Internet. Transmitting personal information over the Internet is done at your own risk. This Policy addresses only our policy and procedures. We are not responsible for the privacy policies of third parties, including but not limited to those whose web sites may be linked to the Website.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**
---------------------------------

If we make any changes to how we treat our registered users’ personal information, we will notify you by email to the primary email address specified in your account and/or through a notice on the Website home page. The date this Policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable email address for you, and for periodically visiting our Website and this Policy to check for any changes.

[About Us](https://myconnectedcaregiver.com/about-us)     [Contact](https://myconnectedcaregiver.com/contact-us)     [Help Center](https://connected-caregiver.helpscoutdocs.com/)     Resources     [For Professional Caregivers](https://myconnectedcaregiver.com/professional-caregivers/)     Open Source Acknowledgements     [Terms & Conditions](https://myconnectedcaregiver.com/terms/)     [Privacy Policy](https://myconnectedcaregiver.com/privacy)     [FAQs](https://myconnectedcaregiver.com/faqs)
